{
    "id": "0497af472f044f90a91d5acf53d2c741",
    "title": "High School Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f8f4e8fd6d014e84b096df2be82e6844",
            "title": "High School Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Don’t forget, ………………………..?",
                    "description": "After a negative imperative we use will you in question tags.",
                    "answers": [
                        "won't you",
                        "can you",
                        "will you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They have got six children ……………………….. are studying music.",
                    "description": "Either structure is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all of whom",
                        "of whom all",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will never forget the day ………………………….. we met.",
                    "description": "After nouns referring to time we can use that instead of when.",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "when",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The reason ……………………………… I dislike you is that you are so bad-tempered.",
                    "description": "Either why or that can be used after that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "why",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please remind me …………………………. the oil.",
                    "description": "Remind is followed by object + infinitive.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to check",
                        "checking",
                        "of checking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………………. me that we hadn’t bought anything to eat.",
                    "description": "To remind somebody is to make them remember.",
                    "answers": [
                        "reminded",
                        "remembered",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You remind me ……………………………… I had met at school.",
                    "description": "Of is required in this structure.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a girl",
                        "of a girl"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a stern man who always ………………………………. me of my headmaster.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "reminds",
                        "remembers",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is a kind woman who always makes me ……………………………. my grandmother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "remind",
                        "remember",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He suggested …………………………… the main car park.",
                    "description": "We cannot use an infinitive after suggest.",
                    "answers": [
                        "me to use",
                        "me using",
                        "that I use"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said ……………………………….. park there.",
                    "description": "We use a that-clause after said.",
                    "answers": [
                        "me not to",
                        "that I must not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He told ……………………………",
                    "description": "Tell can be followed by object + infinitive or object + that clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "me to wait",
                        "me that I should wait",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}